Now go pick up
those move controllers.
Pick out a song
and lose control, yeah!
You'll feel the music
flowing through ya.
And I don't want to
hear any excuses.
Get your ass up,
Move around!
Swing your booty
to the sound!
Reach for the sun,
then drop it down!
Lift your arms
then swing 'em around!
If you don't want to shake it
I take it you want to make it...
Appear as some kind of laid back
and chill dude but it's a straight fact...
That you're whack if you don't check
that all the Box hacking and slashing...
Is better than button mashing
when playing the latest cash in...
By studios, not even caring
if what they're making is fair and...
All the numbers compared,
only some devs really care!
Invite some friends home and share.
The more the merrier!
Today we're gonna
play some Beat Saber!
I don't want to alarm you,
but the way you move your arms...
Makes you look
a little Gaga.
But who cares
as long as you have Fun!
If you want to shake it baby,
You ain't gonna make it, maybe...
You need to embrace it,
you don't have what it takes and run!
The lights are flashing, the music rocks.
A highspeed onslaught of moving blocks.
In all directions, in every spot.
If you missed a few take another shot!
You might want to go for the Highscore.
That's what the Leaderboards are there for.
Ooooohhhhhh...
Baby do it
One More Time!
Up, down, left, right, Headset airtight.
Expert Level rythmic swordfight.
Laser guided swinging system.
Move your arms around and twist them!
Listen to the music flowing.
Keep the Combo-Meter going!
Can you make it through it all?
Avoiding bombs, avoiding walls.
Up, down, left, right, Headset airtight.
Expert Level rythmic swordfight.
Laser guided swinging system.
Move your arms around and twist them!
Listen to the music flowing.
Keep the Combo-Meter going!
Can you make it through it all?
Avoiding bombs, avoiding walls.